<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sips Joeri - Gip site</title>
    <link>http://joeri-sips.github.io/categories/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sips Joeri - Gip site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://joeri-sips.github.io/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    <item>
      <title>IT is life</title>
      <link>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/IT-autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/IT-autobiography/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;Introduction:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Joeri Sips, I am 17 years old and I’m an IT management student at the Immaculata institute in Oostmalle. In my free time I play a game called: “Destiny”in which I was the number one Belgian player last schoolyear but that’s no longer the case since I took a break from the game during the vacation and the other players caught up. And this is an autobiography about what IT was, is and will be in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-experiences:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;First experiences:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think my interest in IT comes from my mother, she is working as a network manager nowadays.
That has been her work for as long as I can remember and longer; she even tells me stories of giving workshops on how to use a mouse. As I was learning mathematics when I was 7 years old, she made a program for me on which I had to solve multiplications and afterwards it checked my work and showed me if my answers were wrong or right. The first sites I used to visit were sites that had fun and small browsergames like Tetris variations or Pin Ball. I sometimes still visit one of those sites called “funnygames.nl” to play Warfare 1917 which used to be my favorite game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;it-now:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;IT now:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years ago I started playing a game called DUST 514 and it that game I met people from the USA, Sweden, Germany and South Africa who are still my friends today. At home I only use the computer 2 hours a day on average and only for school because at school we use them all the time. At home I use my Playstation and my mobile phone most of the time and a while ago my microphone for the playstation broke but I got my phone to work as mic which is cool right? Especially because no one I know knows how to do that except me. Last year I made a small browser game together with two friends and I see that as my biggest achievement thus far even though its just a “click game” and nothing too complicated. I’m just simply baffled with all you can do with IT and I like doing all you can do with it. That’s why I’m an IT student and because of that I’ve spent a lot of time with programs like Word and Excel and when I see other people use it I get nervous ifthey don’t use it in the most efficient and fast way. I like to call myself a power-user because a power-user is someone who knows all the shortcuts and the functionality of a computer and I match those qualities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;future-in-it:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;Future in IT:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the future I’d like to make a living of IT as a programmer and create things that will be used by a lot of people like games. Also I would like to get more hardware because I enjoy playing around with cables and seeing what I can do with different hardware and because boys sure like their toys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If IT wasn’t around now I’d probably be building camps and acting like I am a knight but because it is around it is a big part in my life; it wakes me up, it tells me what to do for school and it even finds me new friends .So I am thankful that I grew up recently and not 100 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://nl.tinypic.com?ref=208v521&#34; target=&#34;blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i66.tinypic.com/208v521.jpg&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;Image and video hosting by TinyPic&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
